<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Secure Tunnel Client</string>
    <string name="title_vpn_settings">Seamless VPN Tunnel API</string>
    <string name="title_local_proxy_settings">Localhost HTTP Proxy API</string>
    
    <string name="label_relay_host">Remote Relay Host</string>
    <string name="label_relay_port">Remote Relay Port</string>
    <string name="label_local_port">Local Proxy Port</string>
    <string name="label_padding_amount">Handshake Padding (bytes)</string>
    <string name="label_insecure_mode">Insecure Mode (Allow Self-Signed TLS)</string>
    <string name="label_save_settings">Save Config</string>
    
    <string name="status_stopped">Disconnected</string>
    <string name="status_running">Running / Engaged</string>
    <string name="button_start">Connect Tunnel</string>
    <string name="button_stop">Disconnect</string>
    
    <string name="app_help_title">Secure Tunnel - Documentation &amp; Setup</string>
    <string name="app_help_body">
        <h3><b>Introduction</b></h3>
        Welcome to <b>Secure Tunnel Android Client</b> (v0.0.3). This application allows you to tunnel your network traffic securely through an encrypted SSL/TLS interface to a remote Secure Relay server. Perfect for bypassing network blocks and protecting data transmission.<br/><br/>

        <h3><b>Modes of Operation</b></h3>
        Choose between two powerful routing techniques based on your security constraints:<br/><br/>
        
        <b>1. Seamless VPN Mode (Android VPN API):</b><br/>
        • <i>Overview:</i> Captures all system-wide TCP and UDP packets seamlessly.<br/>
        • <i>Method:</i> Uses Android\'s native <b>VpnService</b> layer to establish a virtual network adapter. All internet traffic is redirected through the local SOCKS5/HTTP loopback proxy on the device.<br/>
        • <i>Setup:</i> No extra software settings required! Just enable and confirm system permissions.<br/><br/>

        <b>2. Localhost HTTP/SOCKS5 Proxy Mode:</b><br/>
        • <i>Overview:</i> Starts a dual-protocol in-app proxy daemon bound to localhost.<br/>
        • <i>Method:</i> Listens on 127.0.0.1 on your custom configured port.<br/>
        • <i>Setup:</i> Manually configure your web browser, Telegram, or system Wi-Fi proxy settings to route via:<br/>
        &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;<b>Server:</b> 127.0.0.1<br/>
        &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;<b>Port:</b> (Your Configured Port, Default: 19088)<br/><br/>

        <h3><b>Secure Handshake Padding</b></h3>
        To defend against Deep Packet Inspection (DPI) and protocol profiling attacks, the tunnel pads the initial destination route handshake:<br/>
        • All handshake packets are injected with random padding bytes up to 2x your configured option.<br/>
        • Data payloads exceeding 1024 bytes automatically bypass padding to optimize network performance.<br/><br/>

        <h3><b>Certificate Insecurity Options</b></h3>
        • <b>Insecure Mode Enabled:</b> Useful for development with local self-signed TLS certificates (bypasses CA checks).<br/>
        • <b>Insecure Mode Disabled:</b> Strict TLS checks. Recommended for production deployment.
    </string>
</resources>
